- huh you like embaressing me huh ?
- i what now?
- Well whatever you want to do if that's what you wanna do you if you think you can beat me 123 yeah you can fuck me in the ass lets go
- mate i would beat you in a 1v1 easy even with both my hands tied around your neck
- Shut the fuck up boy
- I'll show you who's the boss of this gym
- Oh shit i'm sorry
- yeah you better be kid
- You like challenges ?
- You got me mad now
- i dont even see how the 2 are related
- but lets do this
- Endure the lash of the spanking
- COME ON
- let's go!
- Take it boy
- Swallow my cum
- I'll give you one more round with me
- Come on college boy
- you have gona full on into madness
- never go full into that
- fuck you leather man
- WHAT A GOOD PRETTY BOY RECRUIT



******************************************************************************************************************************************************************************


- Hey, excuse me, big guy. Did you hear some noises going on in here, couple minutes ago? I was in the other room working out.
- Yeah I just finished wrestling some jabroni here and I, uhh.. knocked him out.
- Jabroni?
- Yeah, some guy said he wanted to challenge me to a wrestling match, what about 123? Nothing.
- No, whats with the jabroni thing?
- Well, you know this guy thought he was pretty tough and thought he could take me, so I threw a couple rounds out of him.
- Well you know, most italians do think they're pretty tough, I think I'm pretty tough.
- Yeah? 
- You think you're pretty tough?
- Well, just had a match, a little tired but, ehh.. Could go for another round if that's what you're into.
- Listen I was in the other room if that's what you call a match I got news for you buddy, you ain't ever had nothing like me before.
- Well, maybe you and I should try and settle it then.
- Are you sure you really know what you're getting yourself into?
- Well, I gotta go get my hair cut in about half an hour, but I think I can maybe spare some time.
- Alright, well maybe you can do that after you come out of the hospital.
- Well, lets give it a go.
- Really?
- You're a pretty big guy.
- I'm a pretty big guy, slow you know..
- Yeah but I'm pretty quick, so.
- Well, what do you wanna bet for?
- I don't know, whatever you want.
- Well, I'll tell you what, I seem to be the intellectual of the both of us, I'll tell you what; Let's bet your ass. I win, I take your ass. How's that sound?
- Yeah? You're gonna fuck me in the ass? Is that what you mean?
- You want me to don't you?
- Well, whatever you wanna do, if you think you can beat me 1 2 3, yeah you can fuck me in the ass, we'll go.
- You know what I think you talk too much shit.
- Listen, I'm the roman Greco of wrestling, you wanna just start off right now?
- Sure, you wanna go roman greco?
- Alright, buddy let's go.
- Alright, you're gonna let me start on top, eh?
- You wanna get on bottom? You know that's the point you wanna be.
- Alright, listen you got it come on man!


******************************************************************************************************************************************************************************

-What the hell are you two doing? Get your ass from here now boy, and you too!
 Something you are excited for son?
-No sir.
-You are lying to me! I saw you looking over at pretty boy recruit over there and get turned on.
-Yes sir no sir.
-All of you get your ass down from here now! yells something I don't understand
What the hell do you boys think that this is, fucking Faerie Land? Pulling on your weewees like a pack of fucking (something)
You two obviously want to suck what a real man has so get down on your knees and suck every last drop of my cum until my dick is drained, now!
Disobedience huh? That's a mistake... Get to the quarterdeck now! Move move move!


******************************************************************************************************************************************************************************


Hey buddy, I think you've got the wrong door, the leather club's two blocks down.

Fuck?You?

Oh, Fuck?You leather man. Maybe you and I should settle it right here on the ring if you think your so tough.

Oh yea? I'll kick your ass!

Ha! Yeah right man. Let's go! Why don't you get out of that leather stuff? I'll strip down out of this and we'll settle it right here in the ring. What do you say?

Yeah, no problem buddy!

You got it. Get out of that uh, jabroni outfit.

Yeah, smart ass.

I'll show you who's the boss of this gym.


******************************************************************************************************************************************************************************


My fellow brothers, I, Billy Herrington, stand here today, humbled by the task before us, 

mindful of the sacrifices borne by our Nico Nico ancestors.

We are in the midst of a crisis. Nico Nico Douga is at war against a far-reaching storm of disturbance and deletion. 

Nico Nico's economy is badly weakened: a consequence of carelessness and irresponsibility on the part of acknowledgement, 

but also on the collective failure to make hard choices and to prepare for a new, MAD age.

Today, I say to you, that the challenges are real, and they are many. They will not be easily met, 

or in a short span of time, but know this, Nico Nico: they will be met. 

In reaffirming the greatness of our site, we understand that greatness is never given, 

our journey has never been one of shortcuts. 

It has not been for the faint-hearted, or who seek the fleshly pleasures. Rather, it has been the risk-takers, 

the wasted genii, the creators of MAD things. 

For us, they toiled in sweatshops, endured the lash of the spanking. Time and again, these men struggled, 

and sacrificed, so that we might ... LIVE BETTER.

We remain the most powerful site on the Internet, our minds no less inventive, and services no less needed 

than they were last week, or yesterday, or the day before the day after tomorrow. Starting today, 

we must pull up our pants, dust ourselves off, and begin again the work of remaking Nico Nico Douga.

Now, there are some who question the scale of our ambitions, who suggest our server system cannot tolerate too many movies. 

Their memories are short, for they have forgotten what Nico Nico already has done, 

what free men can achieve when imagination is joined to common purpose.

And so, to all the people who are watching this video, from the grandest cities, 

to the small villages where IKZO was born, know that Nico Nico is a friend to every man, 

who seeks the future of love and peace. 

Now we will begin to responsibly leave authorized common materials to Nico Nico people, 

and forge a hard-earned peace in this MAD world.

What is required of us now is a new era of responsibility. 

This is the price, and the promise, of Nico NiCommons citizenship. 

Nico Nico Douga, in the face of common dangers, in this winter of our hardship, let us remember these timeless words: ASS, WE CAN.

Let it be said by our children's children, that when we were tested by DOS attacks, when we were refused by YouTube, 

that we did not turn back, nor did we falter, and we carried forth that great gift of 

freedom be delivered, and safely to future generations.

Thank you. God bless, and God bless Nico Nico Douga.


******************************************************************************************************************************************************************************



Starring : Billy Herrington - Aniki - BH Bo garret - Choro~n - BO Cameron Sage - Ikeda - IK Steve Cassidy - Tortoise - TO Eric Evans - Ebihara Ebizou - ER Frank Towers - Izumi Deikapurio - FT

Billy is sitting in his office checking some documents knocking 

BH - Come in [Bo appears] 

BO - Hey bro, what's happenin'? 

BH - Hey, come on in. Close the door. 

BO - sure. [Bo sitts on the chair] 

BH - Bo! What the hell are you doing here? 
I told you last time you came by the station drunk as all hell - not to come by! 

BO - Hey can I come by to my big bro once in a while? God, I mean... 
I'm not drunk now, smoked a few... But just came by to say hey 

BH - So let me guess what the problem is this time - dinero. 

BO - It's a loan!
Come on, I'm good for it. You know me, I got a job doing a... 

BH - You know what bro? Just kill that right now because you know what, you're always getting these bullshit jobs that never materialize,ok? 
And you need to get that crap off your arms, those cartoon figures, they're not cutting it. I can get you a job at the cadet program, be fighting fires, you'll love it. 

BO - I love fire... I love fire ... I, I , I just, I, it fascinates me! I, I can't help it. 
It's like...the colours, you know ... I uh...it turns me on .. he he, it does, I don't know why but it does. 

BH - Listen man, I gotta lay something on ya I wanna talk to you... 
Something thats been bothering me. BO - Here we go, another big brother lecture again

********Meanwhile in the corridor of the fire station :

IK - Watch where you're going, fag boy! 

TO - Why don't you get fucked? 'Cause everyone in the station already had a piece of your ass. 

FT - HEY,HEY,HEY Cameron! The chief is right there. 

FT - C'mon honey you want me to fuck you in the ass? C'mon c'mon! 

IK - Shut up fuck head. points at Steve 

IK - And you! you better watch yourself dude, because you're fucking playing with fire with me! Let's go.

Back to the Billy and Bo conversation

BH - Bo... What I'm trying to say is... Bro... It's me, I want to talk to you about me bro. 

BO - You?! What's wrong with brother? You can tell me, whats wrong? 

BH - Well...do you rememeber the time we were hanging out and we got drunk, and I started telling you about... about those feelings. 

BO - What? The gay stuff? 

BH - Well, to tell you the truth it's these fantasies I was telling you about... I'm having them more and more, and uh... 
They're really turning me on... Like the other day, I was in the shower and I was fantasing about everybody else in the 
shower and we were beating off together, and... I like it. You know, the other night one of the boys was sleeping and I... 
Reached out to play with his dick 

BO - Sex is sex! Guys, girls, heh, doesnt matter. Feels good! It's natural, don't worry about it, it's ok. Someone knocking at the door 

BH - Listen, nobody , nobody must know about this, you understand? So keep your fucking mouth shut, I'm serious. 

BH - Come in. Steve enters the office.

TO - Hey chief, sorry to bother you and your company but we've got a scheduling problem we need to talk about. 

BH - Steve, this is my little brother - Bo. He was just leaving. 

BO - I was? Pleasure to meet you- 

TO - Sorry, I'll come back in a bit. 

BH - No no no, no big problem just give me 15 minutes. 

TO - Cool.

Steve leaves the office.

BO - Now there's an ass I wouldn't mind fucking, you know what I mean. 

BH - Well, that's the new cadet. He's gay, and he's been catching a looooot of flak around the station 
from all the other guys too about it because he's cool outta the closet. 

BO - Hey big bro, you and I should take him up on the roof and show him twenty inches of pleasure, you know what I'm saying, hm? 

BH - Yeah, right. You know what? You keep your fucking grubby hands off of him, and get out, and make sure you leave through the back 

BO - Shut your fucking mouth!We share the same blood! Don't pull this fucking high and mighty shit with me, 
You've been this way ever since you became a fireman. Mr big shot firechief, you hate it when things burn. 
Always trying to save the world, well save the world bro, save the world. 

BH - You know what dude? You just dialed the wrong number.Ok? You wanna fuck with me? You're a fucking psycho, ok?
Get of the dope, get of the booze, and I dont give a fuck what you do, but for now, get the fuck out. 

BO - Fuck you. I don't need your fucking shit anyway, big brother.

Bo leaves

At the fire station, Steve and Billy goes somewhere and talk with Cameron who is in the way IK - Hey chief BH - hey whats up bro? Ik - I just saw your brother... in the back of the station with one of our jackets on, and ... well.. he wasn't wearing any pants. BH - Son of a bitch.

Steve walks to Cameron TO - Yo, what's this? Stupid (braider? Rater? I don't know...)

ER - Hey chief, BH - Hey whatsup? ER - Well the arson department faxed over our match on the partial finger prints found. Has any DNA come up on that white slimy stuff? BH - No do me a favor though, take the fax, put it on my desk in my office and I'm gonna go upstairs to work out some bad tension, I need to be alone for a bit. ER - Sure chief, I'll let everyone know to stay clear of the roof BH - Thanks alot ER - ok


*************************************march 6th 2014 BLOP ANNIVERSARY WOOOO*****************************************************************************************************************************************


-Oh shit I'm sorry

-Sorry for what? 

-Our daddy tought us not to be ashamed of our dicks, ‘specially when they are such good size ‘n all. 

-Yeah I can see that, your daddy gave you good advice. 

-It gets bigger when I pull on it. 

-Mmhm. 

-Sometimes, I pull on it so hard, I rip the skin. 

-Well, my daddy taught me a few things too, like how to not rip the skin by using someone else’s mouth, instead of your own hand. 

-Will you show me? 

-I’ll be right happy to.


******************************************UPDATE************************************************************************************

What da hell do ya boyz fink dat dis is, zoging Faerie Land? Pulling on your weeweez like a pack of zoging fruitz?
You two obviouzly want ta suck what da real warboss haz so git down on your kneez and suck every last bullet of ma dakka until my shoota iz drained, now!
Disobediunce huh? Dat's da mistake... Get to da quarterdeck now! Move move move!


**************THIS IS FOR OUR SLAVIC PART OF BLOP, IT WAS SO GOOD THAT I THOUGHT IT DESERVES TO BE PUT IN HERE****************

Не прозвучит задорное фак ю, 
Забудутся ремиксы и видосы, 
Лишь пара строк и старые скриншоты, 
Остались к очень грустному утру. 

И не войдет в качалку ее босс, 
И пара блоков вновь не будут выше, 
И Ван Даркхольм, распластанный на нише, 
Поймет, что данжен скукой весь пророс. 

Побьешь меня на раз-два-три, еще по раунду, тихоня? 
Кожевник - ты забыл про свой наряд! 
А колледж бой, раскрепощенный гад, 
Ушел, закрыв ту door, что цель есть для next boy`я. 

Прислушайтесь! Пусть умер наш герой, 
Но вот в окне услышал стон приятный, 
Ах, Ass we can! - крик всюду многократный, 
Прощай же Билли, босс качалки мой.


